SUCHINLIN

User Experience Designer



PROFILE

A bit about me and my "why" to designing:

I love helping people. Whether it's through projects or even something as simple as a passing greeting, I enjoy uplifting spirits and lightening loads. It's what brought me into nursing and now to user experience design.

Apart from design, I also am an avid runner and enjoy the discipline, expression, and community that comes with it.

SKILLS

Design Tools	Soft Skills
Figma	Empathy
Sketch	Compassion
Invision	Creativity
Procreate	Leadership

UX Skills

- User Research
- Competitive Research
- Comparative Research
- Persona
- Sketching
- Storyboarding
- Prototyping
- Wireframing
- Interaction Design
- Usability Testing

EXPERIENCE

POLLTAB

UX/UI Designer

Feb 2021 to Present

- Analyzed heuristic integrity of client's website desktop and mobile
- Conducted research on 5 competitors and 2 comparators
- Fulfilled client's requests to make users' flow more intuitive and UI more "modern" with 3 key UI design changes updated CTA buttons, imagery, and color-scheme
- Crafted new style guide and logo for brand redesign using Figma

PERSONAL PORTFOLIO DESIGN

UX/UI Designer

May 2020 to Present

- Collaborated with engineer to launch 2 variations of portfolio
- Developed and designed style guidelines (typography, color scheme, and components) and high fidelity prototypes on Figma
- Created personalized icons for portfolio use using Figma

MAKE AMERICA DINNER AGAIN

UX Design Consultant

April 2020

- Spearheaded team of 3 with focus on MVP
- Conducted and synthesized research to guide design decisions
 6 email interviews, 20 responses to custom-made survey, and
 149 responses from client's existing survey
- Ideated design solutions for low to mid fidelity prototype
- Pitched project outcomes and compiled all deliverables for client

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

UX Design Apprentice

Jan - April 2020

- Certified completion of 400 hours of instruction
- Completed 3 solo design projects and 3 team design projects for both mobile and desktop 4 UX/Research, 2 UI predominant

MOUNT SINAI BETH ISRAEL, Cardiac Tele / Stroke Unit

Registered Nurse, Unit Team Lead

Nov 2009 - July 2019

- Redesigned information boards and patient data collection forms
- Researched uptodate practices for policy and procedure committee
- Led team of 14 nurses and support staff through 12 hr day shifts

EDUCATION

B.S. Nursing

General Assembly

UX Design Immersive Jan - Apr 2020

General Assembly

Visual Design Workshop

May 2020

New York University

Sept 2005 - May 2009

Udemy

Drawing and Painting with Procreate May 2021